Art and Architecture of Japan Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Prints (Box 10)
  - Known Artists (Box 10)
    - Torii Kiyoshige, ac. 1720-1760 (Box 11)
      - Shiba Kokan, 1747-1818 (Box 11)
      - Isoda Koryusai, ac. 1764-1788 (Box 11)
      - Onchi Koshiro, 1891-1955 (Box 11)
      - Utagawa Kunimasa, 1773-1810 (Box 11)
      - Gototei Kunisada, 1786-1864 (Box 11)
      - Utagawa Kuniyasu, 1794-1832 (Box 11)
      - Utagawa Kuniyoshi, 1797-1861 (Box 11)
      - Kusama Yayoi, 1929- (Box 11)
      - Kaigetsudo Dohan, ac. 1704-1716 (Box 11)
      - Kitao Masanobu, 1761-1816 (Box 11)
      - Okumura Masanobu, 1690-1768 (Box 11)
      - Masataka, S., ac. ca. 1680-1698 (Box 11)
      - Moromasa (Box 11)
      - Hishikawa Moronobu, 1616-1694 [Slide boxes 65-66] (Box 11)
      - Furayama Moroshige [Slide box 66] (Box 11)
      - Maruyama Okyo, 1733-1795 (Box 11)
      - Toshusai Sharaku, ac. 1794-1795 (Box 11)
      - Kitao Shigemasa, 1739-1820 (Box 11)
      - Nishimura Shigenaga, 1697-1756 (Box 11)
      - Nishimura Shigenobu, 1711-1785 (Box 11)
      - Shinsui, 1898-1977 (Box 11)
      - Shoson (Box 11)
      - Shoun, 1870-1965 (Box 11)
      - Katsukawa Shuncho, ac. 1780-1792 (Box 11)
      - Katsukawa Shunei, 1762-1819 (Box 11)
      - Katsukawa Shunko, 1743-1812 (Box 11)
      - Kubo Shunman, 1757-1820 (Box 11)
      - Katsukawa Shunsho, 1726-1792 [Slide box 67] (Box 12)
      - Tamura Suio, 1716-1789 (Box 12)
      - Nishikawa Sukenobu (Box 12)
      - Okumura Toshinobu, ac. 1717-1750 (Box 12)
      - Utagawa Toyoharu, 1735-1814 (Box 12)
      - Utagawa Toyokuni, 1769-1825 (Box 12)
      - Ishikawa Toyonobu, 1711-1785 (Box 12)
      - Kitagawa Utamaru, 1754-1806 [Slide boxes 67-68] (Box 12)
      - Shibata Zeshin, 1807-1891 [Slide box 68] (Box 12)
- Sculpture (Box 12)
  - Jomon period, ca. 10,500 BCE-400 BCE (Box 12)
    - Early Jomon (Box 12)
      - Various Titles (Box 12)
    - Middle Jomon (Box 12)
      - Various Titles (Box 12)
    - Late Jomon (Box 12)
      - Various Titles (Box 12)
    - Final Jomon (Box 12)
      - Various Titles (Box 12)
  - Kofun period, 300-600 (Box 12)
    - Various Titles (Box 12)
  - Suiko Period, 553-650 (Box 12)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 12)
      - Various Titles (Box 12)
      - Kyoto (Box 12)
        - Minoshima (Box 12)
      - Nara (Box 12)
        - Chugu-ji [Slide box 69] (Box 12)
        - Horyu-ji (Box 12)
      - Osaka (Box 12)
        - Kanshin-ji (Box 12)
        - Shitenno-ji (Box 12)
        - Yachu-ji (Box 12)
      - Tokyo (Box 12)
        - National Museum (Box 12)
    - Known Artists (Box 12)
      - Tori Busshi (Box 12)
        - Various Titles (Box 12)
        - Nara (Box 12)
          - Horyu-ji (Box 12)
  - Hakuho Period, 650-710 (Box 12)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 12)
      - Various Titles (Box 12)
      - Nara (Box 12)
        - Hasedera (Box 12)
        - Horyu-ji (Box 12)
          - Tachibana Shrine (Box 12)
        - Kofuku-ji (Box 12)
        - Oka-dera (Box 12)
        - Toshodai-ji (Box 12)
        - Yakushi-ji [Slide box 70] (Box 12)
        - Jindai-ji (Box 12)
  - Tempyo Period, 710-794 (Box 12)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 12)
      - Various Titles (Box 12)
      - Nara (Box 12)
        - Horyu-ji (Box 12)
        - Kofuku-ji (Box 12)
        - Oka-dera (Box 12)
        - Shin-Yakushi-ji (Box 12)
        - Shorin-ji (Box 12)
        - Taima-ji (Box 12)
        - Todai-ji (Box 12)
          - Various Titles (Box 12)
            - Gigaku Masks (Box 12)
            - Octagonal Lantern [Slide box 71] (Box 12)
          - Daibutsuden (Box 12)
          - Hokkedo (Box 12)
          - Kaidan-in (Box 12)
          - Nigatsudo (Box 12)
        - Toshodai-ji (Box 12)
      - Tokyo (Box 12)
        - National Museum (Box 12)
  - Jogan Period, 794-897 (Box 12)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 12)
      - Various Titles (Box 12)
      - Kyoto (Box 12)
        - Daigo-ji (Box 12)
        - Jingo-ji (Box 12)
        - Kaijyuzan-ji (Box 12)
        - Kyo-o Gokoku-ji (Box 12)
          - Tobatsu Bishamonten (Box 12)
          - 4 Guardian Kings [Slide box 72] (Box 12)
        - Matsuno-o-Jinja (Box 12)
        - Ninna-ji (Box 12)
      - Nara (Box 12)
        - Various Titles (Box 12)
        - Gango-ji (Box 12)
        - Hokke-ji (Box 12)
        - Muro-ji (Box 12)
        - Tachibana-dera (Box 12)
        - Todai-ji (Box 12)
        - Yakushi-ji (Box 12)
        - Zensui-ji (Box 12)
      - Wakayama (Box 12)
        - Kongobuji (Box 12)
        - Seiganto-ji (Box 12)
  - Fujjiwara Period, 898-1185 (Box 12)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 12)
      - Various Titles (Box 12)
      - Boston (Box 12)
      - Hiraizumi [Slide box 73] (Box 13)
      - Kyoto (Box 13)
        - Various Titles (Box 13)
        - Daigo-ji (Box 13)
        - Joruri-ji (Box 13)
    - Known Artists (Box 13)
      - Enkai, ac. 11th century (Box 13)
      - Jocho, d. 1055 (Box 13)
  - Kamakura Period, 1185-1336 (Box 13)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 13)
      - Various Titles (Box 13)
      - Kamakura (Box 13)
      - Kyoto (Box 13)
        - Various Titles (Box 13)
        - Daigo-ji (Box 13)
        - Jingo-ji (Box 13)
        - Jyoruri-ji (Box 13)
        - Myoho-in (Box 13)
      - Nara [Slide boxes 73-74] (Box 13)
      - Shiga [Slide box 74] (Box 13)
      - Tokyo (Box 13)
      - Wakayama (Box 13)
    - Artist Known (Box 13)
      - Genkai, ac. 13th century (Box 13)
      - Gyokai, ac. 13th century (Box 13)
      - Gyokei (Box 13)
      - Inban (Box 13)
      - Inchi, ac. ca. 1252 (Box 13)
      - Inko (Box 13)
      - Injo (Box 13)
      - Insei (Box 13)
      - Jokei (Box 13)
      - Kaikei, ac. ca. 1185-1220 (Box 13)
      - Koben (Box 13)
      - Koen, 1207-ca. 1285 (Box 13)
      - Kokei, ac. 12th century (Box 13)
      - Kosho, ac. 12-13th century (Box 13)
      - Koyu (Box 13)
      - Kyoen [Slide box 75] (Box 13)
      - Tankei (Box 13)
      - Unkei (Box 13)
      - Zen'en, ac. 13th century (Box 13)
      - Zenkei, 1196-1258 (Box 13)
      - Zenshun, ac. 13th century (Box 13)
  - Ashikaga Period, 1336-1598 (Box 13)
    - Unknown Artist (Box 13)
      - Various Titles (Box 13)
  - Tokugawa Period, 1615-1867 (Box 13)
    - Unknown Artist (Box 13)
      - Various Titles (Box 13)
- Minor Arts (Box 13)
  - Tea Ceremony (Box 13)
    - Various Titles (Box 13)
  - Shosoin (Box 13)
    - Various Titles: including handscrolls & Masks [Slide boxes 75-77] (Box 13)
  - Arms & Armor (Box 13)
    - Various Titles (Box 13)
  - Bookbinding (Box 13)
    - Various Titles (Box 13)
  - Calligraphy (Box 13)
    - Various Titles (Box 13)
    - Tempyo, 710-794 (Box 13)
      - Various Titles (Box 13)
    - Jogan, 794-897 (Box 13)
      - Various Titles (Box 13)
    - Fujiwara period, 898-1185 [Slide boxes 77-78] (Box 13)
      - Known Artist [Slide box 78] (Box 13)
        - Various Titles (Box 13)
        - Ono no Michikaze (Box 13)
        - Ki no Tsurayuki (Box 13)
        - Fujiwara Yukinari (Box 13)
    - Kamakura period, 1185-1336 (Box 13)
      - Known Artists (Box 13)
        - Various Titles (Box 13)
    - Ashikaga period, 1336-1573 [Slide box 79] (Box 13)
      - Known Artists (Box 13)
        - Various Titles (Box 13)
    - Momoyama period, 1573-1615 (Box 13)
      - Known Artists (Box 13)
        - Various Titles (Box 13)
    - Tokugawa period, 1615-1867 (Box 13)
      - Known Artists (Box 13)
        - Various Titles (Box 13)
    - Modern period, 1867- (Box 13)
      - Known Artists (Box 13)
        - Various Titles (Box 13)
  - Ceramics (Box 13)
    - Various Titles (Box 13)
    - Jomon period, ca. 10,500 BCE-400 BCE (Box 13)
      - Incipient Jomon (Box 13)
      - Initial Jomon (Box 13)
      - Early Jomon (Box 13)
      - Middle Jomon [Slide boxes 79-80] (Box 13–14)
      - Late Jomon [Slide box 80] (Box 14)
      - Final Jomon (Box 14)
    - Yayoi period, 300 BCE-300 CE (Box 14)
    - Kofun period, 300-600 (Box 14)
    - Tempyo period, 710-794 (Box 14)
    - Jogan period, 794-897 (Box 14)
    - Kamakura period, 1185-1336 (Box 14)
    - Ashikaga period, 1336-1573 (Box 14)
    - Momoyama period, 1573-1615 [Slide boxes 80-81] (Box 14)
      - Shino ware (Box 14)
      - Karatsu ware [Slide box 81] (Box 14)
      - Iga ware (Box 14)
      - Oribe ware (Box 14)
      - Bizen ware (Box 14)
      - Seto ware (Box 14)
      - Known Artists (Box 14)
        - Tanaka Chojiro (Box 14)
        - Hon'ami Koetsu, 1558-1637 (Box 14)
    - Tokugawa period, 1615-1867 (Box 14)
      - Various Titles (Box 14)
      - Old Imari ware (Box 14)
      - Kyoto ware (Kyo-yaki) (Box 14)
      - Nabeshima ware (Box 14)
      - Kakiemon ware (Box 14)
      - Old Kutani ware (Box 14)
      - Known Artists (Box 14)
        - Aoki Mokubei, 1767-1833 (Box 14)
        - Ogata Kenzan, 1663-1743 [Slide boxes 81-82] (Box 14)
        - Ogata Korin, 1658-1716 [Slide box 82] (Box 14)
        - Ninsei, ac. 1630-1690 (Box 14)
  - Games (Box 14)
    - Various Titles (Box 14)
  - Lacquer (Box 14)
    - Ashikaga period, 1336-1573 (Box 14)
      - Various Titles (Box 14)
    - Momoyama Period, 1573-1615 (Box 14)
      - Various Titles (Box 14)
    - Tokugawa period, 1615-1867 (Box 14)
      - Various Titles [Slide boxes 82-83] (Box 14)
      - Known Artists [Slide box 83] (Box 14)
      - Ogata Korin, 1688-1716 (Box 14)
      - Honami Koetsu, 1558-1637 (Box 14)
  - Masks (Box 14)
    - Various Titles (Box 14)
  - Metals (Box 14)
    - Various Titles (Box 14)
  - Netsuke (Box 14)
    - Various Titles [Slide boxes 83-84] (Box 14)
  - Stage Design [Slide box 84] (Box 14)
    - Various Titles (Box 14)
  - Textiles (Box 14)
    - Various Titles (Box 14)
- Architecture (Box 14)
  - General (Box 14)
    - Various Titles (Box 14)
    - Construction (Box 14)
    - Houses (Box 14)
    - Landscape (Box 14)
    - Tombs (Box 14)
  - Locations [Slide box 85] (Box 15)
    - Aichi Prefecture (Box 15)
    - Asuka (Box 15)
    - Bitchu (Box 15)
    - Ehime Prefecture (Box 15)
    - Fujiwara Prefecture (Box 15)
    - Fukui Prefecture (Box 15)
    - Gifu Prefecture (Box 15)
    - Hiei Mountain (Box 15)
    - Hikone Mountain (Box 15)
    - Hiraizumi (Box 15)
    - Hirosaki (Box 15)
    - Hiroshima (Box 15)
    - Itsukushima [Slide boxes 85-86] (Box 15)
    - Itsukushima [Slide box 86] (Box 15)
    - Inuyama (Box 15)
    - Ise (Box 15)
    - Ishikawa Prefecture (Box 15)
    - Izumo (Box 15)
    - Kanagawa Prefecture (Box 15)
    - Kamakura (Box 15)
    - Kumamoto Prefecture (Box 15)
    - Kochi (Box 15)
    - Koya Mountain (Box 15)
    - Kyoto (Box 15)
      - Various [Slide boxes 86-87] (Box 15)
      - Daigoji [Slide box 87] (Box 15)
      - Daikakuji (Box 15)
      - Daitokuji (Box 15)
        - Various (Box 15)
        - Kohoan (Box 15)
        - Daisenin (Box 15)
        - Hojo (Box 15)
        - Ryogenin (Box 15)
        - Ryokoin [Slide boxes 87-88] (Box 15)
        - Shinjuan [Slide box 88] (Box 15)
        - Zuihoin (Box 15)
      - Higashi Honganji (Box 15)
      - Heian Shrine (Box 15)
      - Hojoji (Box 15)
      - Hokaiji (Box 15)
      - Imperial Palace Kyoto (Box 15)
      - Jishoji (Ginkakuji) (Box 15)
        - Ginkaku (Box 15)
        - Togudo (Box 15)
      - Joruriji (Box 15)
      - Kamo Shrine (Box 15)
      - Katsura (Box 15)
        - Various (Box 15)
        - Gepparo (Box 15)
        - Shoiken [Slide boxes 89-90] (Box 15)
        - Shoin buildings [Slide box 90] (Box 15)
        - Shokatei (Box 15)
        - Shokintei (Box 15)
      - Kinkakuji (Box 15)
      - Kiyomizudera (Box 15)
      - Kodaiji [Slide box 91] (Box 16)
      - Kyoogokokuji (Box 16)
      - Manshuin (Box 16)
      - Myohoin (Box 16)
      - Myokian (Box 16)
      - Myoshinji (Box 16)
      - Nanzenji (Box 16)
      - Nijo Castle (Box 16)
      - Nishi Honganji (Box 16)
      - Ryoanji [Slide box 92] (Box 16)
      - Saihoji (Box 16)
      - Sanjusangendo (Box 16)
      - Shimogamo Shrine (Box 16)
      - Shokokuji (Box 16)
      - Shugakuin Villa (Box 16)
      - Shisendo (Box 16)
      - Tenryuji (Box 16)
      - Tofukuji [Slide box 93] (Box 16)
      - Ujigami Shrine (Box 16)
    - Matsue (Box 16)
    - Matsumoto (Box 16)
    - Matsushima (Box 16)
    - Nagano Prefecture (Box 16)
    - Nara (Box 16)
      - Various Titles (Box 16)
      - Gangoji (Box 16)
      - Hokiji (Box 16)
      - Horyuji [Slide boxes 93-94] (Box 16)
      - Kasuga Shrine [Slide box 94] (Box 16)
      - Muroji (Box 16)
      - Taimadera [Slide boxes 94-95] (Box 16)
      - Todaiji [Slide box 95] (Box 16)
        - Various Titles (Box 16)
        - Daibutsuden (Box 16)
        - Hokkedo (Box 16)
        - Nandaimon (Box 16)
        - Shosoin (Box 16)
      - Toshodaiji (Box 16)
      - Yakushiji [Slide boxes 95-96] (Box 16)
    - Nikko [Slide box 96] (Box 16)
      - Various Titles (Box 16)
      - Taiyuin (Box 16)
      - Toshogu (Box 16)
    - Osaka (Box 16)
    - Otsu (Box 16)
    - Shiga Prefecture (Box 16)
      - Various Titles (Box 16)
      - Ishiyamadera (Box 16)
      - Tsukubusuma Shrine (Box 16)
    - Sumoto (Box 16)
    - Tokyo (Box 16)
    - Uji [Slide box 97] (Box 17)
    - Wakayama Prefecture (Box 17)
    - Yamaguchi Prefecture (Box 17)
    - Yatsushiro (Box 17)
    - Yokohama (Box 17)
- Japan 19th and 20th century Collection (Box 17)
  - Architecture (Box 17)
    - By Architect (Box 17)
      - Ando Tadao, 1941- (Box 17)
        - By Project (Box 17)
          - Chapel of the Light (Osaka) (Box 17)
          - Chapel on Mount Rokko (Kobe, Hyogo Pref.) (Box 17)
          - Chikatsu Asura Museum (Osaka) (Box 17)
          - Children's Museum (Himeiji, Hyogo Pref.) (Box 17)
          - Forest of Tombs Museum (Kumamoto) (Box 17)
          - Meditation Space (UNESCO, Paris) (Box 17)
          - Museum of Literature (Himeiji, Hyogo Pref.) (Box 17)
          - Museum of Wood (Hyogo Pref.) (Box 17)
          - Naoshima Contemporary Art Museum (Naoshima, Kagawa Pref., Shikoku) [Slide box 98] (Box 17)
          - Nariwa Museum (Okayama) (Box 17)
          - Water Temple (Awaji, Hyogo Pref.) (Box 17)
          - Rokko Housing (Kobe, Hyogo Pref.) (Box 17)
        - By Location (Box 17)
          - Ashiya, Hyogo Pref. (Box 17)
          - Osaka (Box 17)
      - Isozaki Arata, 1931- (Box 17)
        - Various Titles (Box 17)
        - Computer City (Box 17)
        - City in the Air (Box 17)
        - Fujimi Country Club (Box 17)
        - Fukuoka Mutual Bank (Box 17)
        - Gunma Prefecture Museum of Fine Art (Box 17)
        - Kamioka Town Hall (Box 17)
        - Kitakyushu Central Library [Slide box 99] (Box 17)
        - Oita Prefectural Library (Box 17)
        - Shukosha Building (Box 17)
        - Western Japan Exhibition Center (Box 17)
      - Kurokawa Kisho, 1934- (Box 17)
        - Various Titles (Box 17)
      - Tange Kenzo, 1913-2005 (Box 17)
        - Various Titles (Box 17)
        - EXPO 1970 (Box 17)
        - Kofu, Yamanashi Communication Center [Slide boxes 99-100] (Box 17)
        - Kurashiki, Town Hall [Slide box 100] (Box 17)
        - Nichinan, Cultural Center (Box 17)
    - By Location (Box 17)
      - Fukuoka (Box 17)
      - Gifu (Box 17)
      - Hofu (Box 17)
      - Kagawa (Box 17)
      - Kobe, Hyogo Prefecture (Box 17)
      - Kumamoto (Box 17)
      - Kyoto (Box 17)
      - Miyakondojo (Box 17)
      - Nara (Box 17)
      - Nagasaki (Box 17)
      - Osaka (Box 17)
      - Sapporo (Box 17)
      - Shimane (Box 17)
      - Suzaka, Nara Prefecture [Slide box 101] (Box 17)
      - Takamatsu (Box 17)
      - Tokyo (Box 17)
        - Hotels (Box 17)
        - Houses (Box 17)
        - Office Buildings (Box 17)
      - Tomamu, Hokkaido Prefecture [Slide box 102] (Box 17)
      - Totsuka (Box 17)
      - Tsukuba (Box 17)
      - Yatsushiro (Box 17)
  - Calligraphy (Box 17)
    - Inoue Yuichi, 1916-1985 (Box 17)
  - Conceptual Art (Box 17)
    - Akasegawa Genpei, 1937- (Box 17)
    - AY-O, 1931- (Box 17)
    - Fluxus (Box 17)
    - HI RED CENTER group (Box 17)
    - Kosugi Takehisa, 1938- (Box 17)
    - Ono Yoko, 1933- (Box 17)
    - Shiomi Mieko, 1938- (Box 17)
  - Film (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous Works (Box 17)
  - Furniture (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous Works (Box 17)
  - Installations (Art) (Box 17)
    - Gutai (Box 17)
    - Kawaguchi Tatsuo, 1940- (Box 17)
    - Kikuhata Mokuma, 1934- (Box 17)
    - Kuboto Shigeko, 1937- (Box 17)
    - Kusama Yayoi, 1929- (Box 17)
    - Lee, U Fan, 1936- (Box 17)
    - Motonaga Sadamasa, 1922- (Box 17)
    - Narita Katsuhiko, 1944-1992 (Box 17)
    - Takamatsu Jiro, 1936- (Box 17)
    - Tanaka Atsuko, 1932- (Box 17)
    - Saito Yoshishige, 1904- (Box 17)
    - Yoshida Katsuro, 1943- (Box 17)
    - Yoshihara Michio, 1933- (Box 17)
  - Painting (Box 17)
    - Ai Mitsu, 1907-1946 (Box 17)
    - Akamatsu Rinsaku, 1878-1953 (Box 17)
    - Aodo Denzen, 1748-1822 (Box 17)
    - Aoki Shigeru, 1882-1911 (Box 17)
    - Arakawa Shusaku, 1936- [Slide boxes102-103] (Box 17–18)
    - Asai Chu, 1856-1907 [Slide box 103] (Box 18)
    - Asaoka Keiko, 1945- (Box 18)
    - Domoto Hisao, 1928- (Box 18)
    - Domoto Insho, b. 1891 (Box 18)
    - Ebihara Kinosuke, 1904-1970 (Box 18)
    - Fujishima Takeji, 1867-1943 (Box 18)
    - Fujita Tsuguji (Tsuguharu), 1886-1968 (Box 18)
    - Fukuda Heihachiro, 1892-1972 (Box 18)
    - Fukuzawa Ichiro, 1898-1992 (Box 18)
    - Fuwa Akira, 1901-1979 (Box 18)
    - Goseda Yoshimatsu, 1855-1915 (Box 18)
    - Harada Naojiro, 1863-1899 (Box 18)
    - Hasegawa Saburo, 1906-1957 (Box 18)
    - Hasegawa Toshiyuki, 1891-1940 (Box 18)
    - Hashimoto Gaho, 1835-1908 (Box 18)
    - Hashimoto Meiji, 1904-1991 (Box 18)
    - Hayami Gyoshu, 1894-1935 (Box 18)
    - Hieda Kazuho, 1920- (Box 18)
    - Hirafuku Hiyakusui, 1877-1933 (Box 18)
    - Hirayama Ikuo, 1930- [Slide box 104] (Box 18)
    - Hirota Tatsu, 1904-1990 (Box 18)
    - Hishida Shunso, 1874-1911 (Box 18)
    - Hyakutake Kenko (Kaneyuki), 1842-1887 (Box 18)
    - Ikeda Shoen, 1888-1917 (Box 18)
    - Imamura Shiko, 1880-1916 (Box 18)
    - Imao Keinen, 1845-1924 (Box 18)
    - Ishigaki Eitaro, 1893-1958 (Box 18)
    - Ito Shoha, 1877-1968 (Box 18)
    - Ito Shinsui, 1898-1972 (Box 18)
    - Kaburagi (Kaburaki) Kiyoka, 1878-1973 (Box 18)
    - Kajiwara Hisako, 1896-1988 (Box 18)
    - Kanayama Akira, 1924- (Box 18)
    - Kanabara Tai, 1898-1997 (Box 18)
    - Kano Hogai, 1828-1888 (Box 18)
    - Kanokogi Takeshiro, 1874-1941 (Box 18)
    - Kataoka Tamako, 1905- (Box 18)
    - Katayama Nanpu, 1887-1980 (Box 18)
    - Kawabata Gyokusho, 1842-1913 (Box 18)
    - Kawabata Ryushi, 1885-1966 (Box 18)
    - Kawaguchi Kigai, 1892-1966 (Box 18)
    - Kawai Gyokudo, 1873-1957 (Box 18)
    - Kawamura Kiyo-o, 1852-1934 (Box 18)
    - Kayama Matazo, 1927- (Box 18)
    - Kikuchi Keigetsu, 1879-1955 (Box 18)
    - Kishida Ryusei, 1891-1929 [Slide box 105] (Box 18)
    - Kitawaki Noboru, 1901-1951 (Box 18)
    - Kobayakawa Shusei, 1889-1974 (Box 18)
    - Kobayashi Kokei, 1883-1957 (Box 18)
    - Koga Harue, 1895-1933 (Box 18)
    - Koide Narashige, 1887-1931 (Box 18)
    - Koito Gentaro, 1887-1978 (Box 18)
    - Kojina Zenzaburo, 1893-1962 (Box 18)
    - Kosugi Misei, 1881-1964 (Box 18)
    - Kudo Kojin, 1915- (Box 18)
    - Kume Keiichiro, 1866-1934 (Box 18)
    - Kuniyoshi Yasuo, 1889-1953 [Slide box 106] (Box 18)
    - Kuroda Seiki, 1866-1924 (Box 18)
    - Kusama Yayoi, 1929- (Box 18)
    - Kuwayama, Tadaaki (Box 18)
    - Kuwayama Tadasuke, 1935- (Box 18)
    - Lee U Fan (Box 18)
    - Maeda Kanji, 1896-1930 (Box 18)
    - Maeda Seison, 1885-1977 (Box 18)
    - Maruki Iri, 1901-1995 (Box 18)
    - Matsumoto Shunsuke, 1912-1948 (Box 18)
    - Matsuoka Hisashi, 1862-1944 (Box 18)
    - Mikishi (Migishi) Kotaro, 1902-1934 (Box 18)
    - Miki Tomio, 1938-1978 (Box 18)
    - Mitsutani Kunishiro, 1874-1936 (Box 18)
    - Miyake Kokki (Katsumi), 1874-1954 (Box 18)
    - Miyamoto Saburo, ac. ca. 1942- [Slide box 107] (Box 18)
    - Morita Kohei, 1916-1994 (Box 18)
    - Morita Shiryu, 1912- (Box 18)
    - Motonaga Sadamasa, 1922- (Box 18)
    - Murakami Kagaku, 1888-1939 (Box 18)
    - Murayama Kaita, 1896-1919 (Box 18)
    - Murayama Tomoyoshi, 1901-1977 (Box 18)
    - Nagata Isshu, 1903-1988 (Box 18)
    - Nakajima Kiyoshi, 1899-1989 (Box 18)
    - Nakamura Ken'ichi, 1895-1967 (Box 18)
    - Nakanishi Natsuyuki, 1935- (Box 18)
    - Nakamura Tsune, 1887-1924 (Box 18)
    - Okada Kenzo, 1902-1982 (Box 18)
    - Okada Saburosuke, 1912-1948 (Box 18)
    - Okamoto Shinso, 1894-1933 (Box 18)
    - Okamoto Taro, 1911-1996 (Box 18)
    - Okumura Togyu, 1889-1990 (Box 18)
    - Ogura Yuki, 1895-2000 (Box 18)
    - Ono Chikkyo, 1889-1979 (Box 18)
    - Onosato toshinobu, 1912- (Box 18)
    - Omoda Seiju, 1891-1933 (Box 18)
    - Saeki Yuzo, 1898-1928 [Slide boxes 107-108] (Box 18)
    - Saito Yoshishige, 1904- [Slide box 108] (Box 18)
    - Sakamoto Hanjiro, 1882-1969 (Box 18)
    - Sakata Kazuo, 1889-1956 (Box 18)
    - Sekine Shoji, 1899-1919 (Box 18)
    - Shiba Kokan, 1747-1818 (Box 18)
    - Shimamoto Shozo, 1928- (Box 18)
    - Shimomura Kanzan, 1873-1930 (Box 18)
    - Shinoda Toko, 1913- (Box 18)
    - Shinohara Ushio, 1932- (Box 18)
    - Shiraga Kazuo, 1924- (Box 18)
    - Shiraga Kazuo, 1924- (Box 18)
    - Soyama Yukihiko, 1859-1892 (Box 18)
    - Sugito Hiroshi, 1970- (Box 18)
    - Sugiyama Yashushi, 1909- (Box 18)
    - Suian (Hirafuku Suian), 1844-1890 (Box 18)
    - Suzuki Makoto, 1897-1969 (Box 18)
    - Suzuki Makoto, 1897-1969 (Box 18)
    - Takayama Tatsuo, 1912- (Box 18)
    - Takehisa Yumeiji, 1884-1934 (Box 18)
    - Takeuchi Seiho, 1864-1942 [Slide boxes 108-109] (Box 18–19)
    - Tanaka Atsuko, 1932- [Slide box 109] (Box 19)
    - Tenshin Okakura, 1862-1913 (Box 19)
    - Teshigahara Sofu, 1900-1979 (Box 19)
    - Togo Seiji, 1897-1978 (Box 19)
    - Tokuoka Shinsen, 1986-1972 (Box 19)
    - Tomioka Tessai, 1836-1924 (Box 19)
    - Tsuchida Bakusen, 1887-1936 (Box 19)
    - Uemura Shoen, 1875-1949 (Box 19)
    - Umehara Ryuzaburo, 1888-1986 (Box 19)
    - Wada Eisaku, 1874-1959 (Box 19)
    - Wada Sanzo (Box 19)
    - Wakasugi Isohachi, 1759-1805 (Box 19)
    - Wakita Kazu, 1908- (Box 19)
    - Watanabe Kazan, 1793-1841 (Box 19)
    - Watanabe Shotei, 1851-1918 (Box 19)
    - Yamaguchi Kayo, 1899-1984 (Box 19)
    - Yamaguchi Takeo, 1902-1983 (Box 19)
    - Yamamoto Hosui, 1850-1906 [Slide boxes 109-110] (Box 19)
    - Yamamoto Kyujin, 1900-1986 [Slide box 110] (Box 19)
    - Yamamoto Shunkyo, 1871-1933 (Box 19)
    - Yamamura Koka, 1886-1942 (Box 19)
    - Yamashita Shintaro (Box 19)
    - Yanase Masamu, 1900-1945 (Box 19)
    - Yasuda Yukihiko, 1884-1978 (Box 19)
    - Yasui Sotaro, 1888-1955 (Box 19)
    - Yokoo Tadanori, 1936- (Box 19)
    - Yokoyama Matsusaburo (Box 19)
    - Yokoyama Taikan, 1868-1958 (Box 19)
    - Yorozo Tetsugoro, 1885-1927 [Slide boxes 110-111] (Box 19)
    - Yoshida Toshio, 1928- [Slide box 111] (Box 19)
    - Yoshida Yoshihiko, 1912- (Box 19)
    - Yoshihara Jiro, 1905-1972 (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous (Collateral) (Box 19)
  - Performance Art (Box 19)
    - Hijikata Tatsumi, 1928-1986 (Box 19)
    - Kubota Shigeko, 1937- (Box 19)
    - Kusama Yayoi, 1929- (Box 19)
    - Murakami Saburo, 1925- (Box 19)
    - Ono Yoko, 1933- (Box 19)
    - Yoshimura Masunobu, 1932- (Box 19)
  - Photography (Box 19)
    - Known Artist (Box 19)
      - Fukuhara Shinzo, 1883-1946 (Box 19)
      - Hidaka Chotaro, 1883-1926 (Box 19)
      - Hosoe Eikoh, 1933- (Box 19)
      - Kosaki Shotaro, 1907- (Box 19)
      - Kumazawa Maroni, 1895-1958 (Box 19)
      - Kurokawa Suizan, 1882-1949 (Box 19)
      - Mori Mariko, 1967- (Box 19)
      - Morimura Yasumasa, 1951- [Slide boxes 111-112] (Box 19)
      - Sakai Tokio, 1898-1991 [Slide box 112] (Box 19)
      - Shimamura Hoko, 1890-1944 (Box 19)
      - Tomatsu Shomei, 1930- (Box 19)
      - Hobo Goro, 1892-1973 (Box 19)
      - Kon Michiko, 1955- (Box 19)
      - Nojima Yasuzo, 1889-1964 (Box 19)
      - Yoshino Makoto (Box 19)
    - Unknown Artist (Box 19)
      - Various Titles (Box 19)
  - Sculpture (Box 19)